[
    {
        "problem": "1+23",
        "solution": 24
    },
    {
        "problem": "30 - 6",
        "solution": 24
    },
    {
        "problem": "2 * 27",
        "solution": 54
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 * 52",
        "solution": 208
    },
    {
        "problem": "13 - 6",
        "solution": 7
    },
    {
        "problem": "9 * 53",
        "solution": 477
    },
    {
        "problem": "71 - 7",
        "solution": 64
    },
    {
        "problem": "7 - 2",
        "solution": 5
    },
    {
        "problem": "108 / 3",
        "solution": 36
    },
    {
        "problem": "426 / 6",
        "solution": 71
    },
    {
        "problem": "176 / 8",
        "solution": 22
    },
    {
        "problem": "8 * 90",
        "solution": 720
    },
    {
        "problem": "873 / 9",
        "solution": 97
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 * 76",
        "solution": 304
    },
    {
        "problem": "6 * 46",
        "solution": 276
    },
    {
        "problem": "522 / 6",
        "solution": 87
    },
    {
        "problem": "66 / 2",
        "solution": 33
    },
    {
        "problem": "82 / 2",
        "solution": 41
    },
    {
        "problem": "6 * 86",
        "solution": 516
    },
    {
        "problem": "3 + 19",
        "solution": 22
    },
    {
        "problem": "89 - 9",
        "solution": 80
    },
    {
        "problem": "3 + 58",
        "solution": 61
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 * 78",
        "solution": 312
    },
    {
        "problem": "8 * 11",
        "solution": 88
    },
    {
        "problem": "7 + 87",
        "solution": 94
    },
    {
        "problem": "8 * 41",
        "solution": 328
    },
    {
        "problem": "12 / 2",
        "solution": 6
    },
    {
        "problem": "3 * 99",
        "solution": 297
    },
    {
        "problem": "7 * 39",
        "solution": 273
    },
    {
        "problem": "656 / 8",
        "solution": 82
    },
    {
        "problem": "8 + 9",
        "solution": 17
    },
    {
        "problem": "873 / 9",
        "solution": 97
    },
    {
        "problem": "2 * 23",
        "solution": 46
    },
    {
        "problem": "38 - 4",
        "solution": 34
    },
    {
        "problem": "64 - 5",
        "solution": 59
    },
    {
        "problem": "72 / 6",
        "solution": 12
    },
    {
        "problem": "7 + 85",
        "solution": 92
    },
    {
        "problem": "97 - 6",
        "solution": 91
    },
    {
        "problem": "2 + 29",
        "solution": 31
    },
    {
        "problem": "9 * 29",
        "solution": 261
    },
    {
        "problem": "77 - 3",
        "solution": 74
    },
    {
        "problem": "65 - 6",
        "solution": 59
    },
    {
        "problem": "54 - 7",
        "solution": 47
    },
    {
        "problem": "148 / 4",
        "solution": 37
    },
    {
        "problem": "36 / 9",
        "solution": 4
    },
    {
        "problem": "9 * 33",
        "solution": 297
    },
    {
        "problem": "7 * 40",
        "solution": 280
    },
    {
        "problem": "53 - 4",
        "solution": 49
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 * 66",
        "solution": 264
    },
    {
        "problem": "34 - 8",
        "solution": 26
    },
    {
        "problem": "5 * 97",
        "solution": 485
    },
    {
        "problem": "2 * 63",
        "solution": 126
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 * 47",
        "solution": 188
    },
    {
        "problem": "190 / 2",
        "solution": 95
    },
    {
        "problem": "3 + 61",
        "solution": 64
    },
    {
        "problem": "9 * 29",
        "solution": 261
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 + 8",
        "solution": 12
    },
    {
        "problem": "9 * 5",
        "solution": 45
    },
    {
        "problem": "3 + 76",
        "solution": 79
    },
    {
        "problem": "94 - 2",
        "solution": 92
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 * 35",
        "solution": 140
    },
    {
        "problem": "6 + 62",
        "solution": 68
    },
    {
        "problem": "11 - 7",
        "solution": 4
    },
    {
        "problem": "17 - 4",
        "solution": 13
    },
    {
        "problem": "8 * 4",
        "solution": 32
    },
    {
        "problem": "6 + 79",
        "solution": 85
    },
    {
        "problem": "6 + 71",
        "solution": 77
    },
    {
        "problem": "44 - 9",
        "solution": 35
    },
    {
        "problem": "6 - 5",
        "solution": 1
    },
    {
        "problem": "11 - 4",
        "solution": 7
    },
    {
        "problem": "71 - 9",
        "solution": 62
    },
    {
        "problem": "44 / 2",
        "solution": 22
    },
    {
        "problem": "29 - 5",
        "solution": 24
    },
    {
        "problem": "427 / 7",
        "solution": 61
    },
    {
        "problem": "3 + 46",
        "solution": 49
    },
    {
        "problem": "6 * 4",
        "solution": 24
    },
    {
        "problem": "5 * 6",
        "solution": 30
    },
    {
        "problem": "5 * 19",
        "solution": 95
    },
    {
        "problem": "3 * 54",
        "solution": 162
    },
    {
        "problem": "36 - 3",
        "solution": 33
    },
    {
        "problem": "79 - 9",
        "solution": 70
    },
    {
        "problem": "5 * 57",
        "solution": 285
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 + 59",
        "solution": 63
    },
    {
        "problem": "2 + 23",
        "solution": 25
    },
    {
        "problem": "77 - 9",
        "solution": 68
    },
    {
        "problem": "115 / 5",
        "solution": 23
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 + 52",
        "solution": 56
    },
    {
        "problem": "3 + 36",
        "solution": 39
    },
    {
        "problem": "5 * 33",
        "solution": 165
    },
    {
        "problem": "7 * 99",
        "solution": 693
    },
    {
        "problem": "6 * 77",
        "solution": 462
    },
    {
        "problem": "8 + 20",
        "solution": 28
    },
    {
        "problem": "150 / 5",
        "solution": 30
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 + 50",
        "solution": 54
    },
    {
        "problem": "243 / 3",
        "solution": 81
    },
    {
        "problem": "4 + 96",
        "solution": 100
    },
    {
        "problem": "49 - 7",
        "solution": 42
    },
    {
        "problem": "36 / 4",
        "solution": 9
    },
    {
        "problem": "180 / 9",
        "solution": 20
    },
    {
        "problem": "3 * 8",
        "solution": 24
    },
    {
        "problem": "6 + 73",
        "solution": 79
    }
]